#### Contact

jeremy.rountree@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jeremy-rountree-0b856a63 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Hospitals
Healthcare Management
Nursing

# Jeremy Rountree

Asst. Chief Nursing Officer at Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

## Summary

Experienced Administrator and RN with a background in Emergency Services and Preparedness. Demonstrated history of working in the hospital & prehospital health care industry. Former Director of Emergency Services, Cardiac Cath Lab and Firefighter. Skilled in Nursing Education and Leadership, Board Certified in Emergency Nursing (CEN), ENPC Instructor, TNCC, ACLS, PALS, JCAHO, CMS, TDH, Emergency Medicine, and Physician/EMS Relations. Leadership position in the Emergency Medical Task Force (EMTF-2), Medical Incident Support Team (M-IST), Strong research professional graduated from the University of Texas Tyler and University of Texas Arlington.

### Experience

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) 8 years 2 months

Asst. Chief Nursing Officer September 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months) Irving, Texas

Director of Emergency Services and Cardiac Cath Lab April 2012 - September 2017 (5 years 6 months)

Primary Stroke Center, Chest Pain Center

Las Colinas Medical Center 6 years 7 months Manager of Emergency Services May 2011 - April 2012 (1 year)

ER Charge/Staff Nurse October 2010 - May 2011 (8 months)

**ER Tech** 

October 2005 - October 2010 (5 years 1 month)

City of Highland Village Fire Dept.
Firefighter
May 2004 - October 2010 (6 years 6 months)

#### Education

University of Texas at Tyler MBA- Healthcare Administration

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Brookhaven Community College
Emergency Medical Technology/Technician (EMT Paramedic)